♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
——·@孙悟空&旗木译制·——
嘿 Daria 我今天没看见你
Hey, Daria. I didn't see you today.
你说过要来摄影大会讨论年鉴的事来着
You said you might come to the photography meeting for yearbook.
是呀 可等牙医关掉话匣子时
Yes, well, when the dentist turned off the gas,
我就改变了心意
I had a change of heart.
但这很有趣的 而且对你成绩也有好处
But it's fun, and it looks good on your transcript.
我对这两件事都有抵触
I'm against both those things.
自由摄影和冲印呢
Free film and developing.
如果你父母发现你在考虑这件事
And if your parents find out that you're even considering it,
你还很有可能搞到一笔可观的贿赂
you could probably squeeze some tremendous bribe out of them.
我再考虑考虑
I'll think about it.
真不敢相信你们竟然想贿赂我... 拿毛票儿
I can't believe you're trying to bribe me... with singles.
甜心 这不是贿赂 这是约定
Sweetie, it's not a bribe, it's a deal.
老实说 你比我的客户还糟糕
Honestly, you're worse than my clients.
对不起
I'm sorry.
年鉴完全扭曲了真实的高中生活
Yearbooks completely distort the reality of high school.
当然了 年鉴经历能为个人网站提供素材
Of course, the yearbook experience could provide material for a web page...
要是有软件就好了
if I had the software.
那就买软件吧
Software it is!
约美男 不能聊咯 再见
Big date! Can't talk! Bye!
嘿 你是Daria对吧?
Hey! You're Daria, right?
我是Ted 图片编辑
I'm Ted, the photo editor.
我看过你的照片
I saw your pictures.
废话不多说 直接解雇我吧
Then cut the small talk and get straight to firing me.
真是好笑 因为你说的和我要说的完全相反 了解?
That's funny, because it's the exact opposite of the truth, right?
你在玩黑色幽默吧 对吗?
You're using sarcasm, aren't you?
事实上 我刚才说得蛮认真的
Actually, I was being sincere for once.
你哪个星球来的?
What planet are you from?
星球? 嘿 又用了夸张 很有意思嘛
Planet? Hey! Hyperbole! Very interesting.
但说真的 我很喜欢你的照片
But, seriously, though, I loved your photos.
你的作品看起来有种西班牙风格
Your composition seems very Spanish,
和弗朗西斯科·戈雅的农民画没什么不同
not unlike the peasant paintings of Francisco Goya.
西班牙浪漫主义画家
我是戈雅的头号粉丝 你呢?
I'm a huge Goya fanatic. You?
嗯... 是 头号粉
Um... yeah, huge.
戈雅的描绘主题多为死亡 毁灭 残忍
Actually, Goya liked to paint death, destruction, brutality.
你应该交点有学问的笔友
You'd have made good pen pals.
有意思的是 他从不去学校上课
And the interesting part is, he's never been to school.
戈雅作品集
直到现在都是他父母在家里教他
His parents have taught him at home until now.
这难道不酷吗?
Isn't that kind of cool?
我向来根据结果断事 所以我得说... 不酷
I judge things by results, so I would have to say... no.
嘿 黑色幽默 你俩肯定有得聊
Hey, sarcasm. You two would get along.
要是他让你入邪教了 网页软件能让给我吗?
If he makes you join his cult, can I have your web page software?
他不在什么邪教
He doesn't belong to a cult.
那个包装看起来也不像什么软件
And the shrink-wrap never comes off that software.
真能拿到的话 我会立马去换成杀人游戏盘
Soon as I get it, I'm exchanging it for Cannibal Fragfest on CD-ROM.
电脑极端暴力
Computer ultra-violence.
戈雅肯定会喜欢的
Goya would have loved that.
嗯 既然你问了
Well, since you ask,
我有在尝试营造出明暗的高度对比
I was kind of trying to get a high contrast of light and dark.
奥古斯都时期第三个重要诗人
漂亮 你肯定读了不少奥维德的诗篇
Neat! You must read a lot of Ovid.
奥芬巴赫所作轻歌剧
我六岁时读了《地狱中的奥菲欧》现在仍然萦绕耳畔
I read Orpheus in the Underworld when I was six, and it still haunts me.
呃 是啊 我也是
Uh, yeah. Me, too.
话说 我得和父母谈谈让我进学校接受正规教育了
You know, I had to talk my parents into let me go to a normal school.
几号开学?
When do you start?
黑色幽默 但我喜欢
Irony! But I like it here.
我只希望志愿活动或募捐活动
I only wish that volunteering or charity fundraising
在年鉴上获得和运动队 俱乐部同样多的版面
got as much yearbook space as sports and clubs.
来吧
Come on!
DeMartino老师?
Mr. DeMartino?
Daria和我刚才在谈学校有些学生
Daria and I were just saying that there are some students at school
真的与众不同
who are really making a difference,
或许我们在年鉴里对他们过于轻描淡写了
and maybe we're short-changing them a little bit in the yearbook.
真高尚啊
How noble.
或许你觉得我们应该缩减运动队和俱乐部的版面
Perhaps you think we should cut some pages from sports and clubs
为他们腾空间?
to make more room?
嘿 好主意 先生
Hey! Good idea, sir!
我们暂停并深思一下 各位
Let me pause and reflect. Everyone!
运动队和俱乐部版面缩减十页
Sports and clubs are cut by ten pages!
- 不能啊 - 这太不公平了
- You can't do that! - But that's not fair!
不是我主意
Not my idea!
你们是被自己的同类妨害的
You've been sabotaged by your own kind.
是他们想到的
They thought of it.
这点子会很赞的
This is going to be great!
好啊
Hello?
你好 叛徒
Hello, traitor.
对叛徒来说真是好天儿 不是吗?
It's a nice day, isn't it... for a traitor.
我压根没信仰过的东西 何谈背叛?
How can I betray something I don't believe in?
友情提示一下 运动队就好像年鉴的跳动的心...
In case you didn't know, sports are, like, the beating heart of the yearbook...
...心脏
um, system!
没错 而且加入法语俱乐部...
Plus, it's like getting in the yearbook is the only reason
为的就是能上年鉴
to join French Club in the first place!
天啊 Brittany 你对法国人和他们文化的深厚感情呢?
Gee, Brittany, what about your deep love for French people and their culture?
对不起... 年鉴危机都把人家搞凌乱了
Sorry... this yearbook crisis is just messing me up!
没事的 宝贝
It's all right babe.
看到你做什么了吗? 叛徒
See what you've done? Traitor!
简直是无礼
It's totally rude!
真是可恶
Completely heinous.
似乎Daria这个女孩根本不明事理什么的
It's like this girl Daria doesn't understand reason, or something.
我听说她是个书呆子
Well, I hear she's a brain.
跟书呆子说不上道理的
You can't reason with brains.
我还是要找她谈谈
I'm still going to talk to her.
作为时尚俱乐部主席 我还是有点震慑力的
As president of the Fashion Club, I can be kind of intimidating.
你绝对唬得住人 Sandi
Oh, you're definitely scary, Sandi.
不过我觉得这案例很特殊 我来做工作吧
But I think this is a special case, so let me talk to her.
要是能交给我做 我会很感激的
It would mean so much if you let me try.
你最好了
You're the best.
哪有 你啦
No, you.
但你不会是认真的吧
But you can't be serious about this.
听着 Ted说的有道理
Listen, Ted has a point.
都是因为那个男孩
It's that boy.
搞半天你就是喜欢人家 对吧?
So, it's all about love, is it?
不是喜欢
It is not about love.
好吧 让你那点小秘密停留在永恒里吧
All right, keep it your secret to cherish always.
但就因为你要出去约会...
But just because you're going out...
Ted和我没在约会
Ted and I are not going out.
随便了
Whatever.
拜托告诉"心水男" 我们要夺年鉴回来
Just tell "loverboy" we want our yearbook back.
这话有语病诶
Did you hear that?
你把动词"夺"和名词"年鉴"连起来用了
You just used the verb "want" with the noun "book."
跟你的男朋友去玩数字游戏吧
Save the math games for your boyfriend.
天呐 真高兴你能过来
Gosh, I'm glad you could come over.
找路没太费周折吧?
Did you have any trouble finding it?
你家前院的玉米快没过我的脑袋了
The corn growing in your front yard sort of tipped me off.
是啊 我家后院种的是南瓜和豆子
Yeah. We keep the squash and beans in the back.
我脑袋里满满都是想要和你分享的摄影点子
I've got all these photo ideas that I want to tell you about.
罗斯福从政时期的政府部门
我觉得促进就业局那种风沙侵蚀的黑白纪录片风格最完美了
I think a WPA black-and-white dust bowl documentary style would be perfect!
好吧 嘿 这是什么?
Um, yeah. Hey, what's this?
我爸和我一起做的留声机啦
Oh, that's the phonograph my dad and I made,
听别人口里描述的电视机 这个一点也不差
and from what I've heard about television, this is just as good!
嘿 我这儿有一些古乐器演奏的早期音乐
Hey, I have some early music played on period instruments.
听了会有种你就站在古大提琴旁边的感觉
You feel like you're right there in front of the viola da gamba!
其实Ted 还是安安静静比较好
Actually, Ted, maybe just quiet.
沙发居然是全木的
This couch is all wood.
是你和你爸做的 对不对?
You and your dad made it, didn't you?
长叶松木 很绵软
Georgia pine! Very soft.
好吧 够了
Okay, that does it.
抱歉 Ted 我跟你不在一个轨道
I'm sorry Ted; I can't keep up with you.
不在一个轨道? 说什么啦?
Keep up? What are you talking about?
你才是超群的那个
You're the remarkable one.
我是说 希望你不要误解 但你真的是个全才
I mean, please don't take this wrong, but you've got it all.
谢谢 给 来片口香糖吗?
Um, thanks. Here, want some gum?
我想等话全都说明白了
I guess when all is said and done,
我们会发现其实我们只是普通美国高中生
we're just a couple of ordinary American teenagers.
对吧?
Right?
Ted?
这就是口香糖
So this is gum!
好喜欢 妈 爸 口香糖 我吃口香糖了
I like it! Mom! Dad! Gum! I got gum!
Morgendorffer家嘛?
Morgendorffers?
以环保工作为主的国际性非政府组织
你们是绿色和平组织的吗? 我家来过人了
If this is for Greenpeace, uh, we've already given.
绿色和平? 那帮蝇营狗苟的家伙?
Greenpeace? Those corporate puppets?
我们认识二位嘛?
Do we know you?
Leslie Dewitt
Leslie Dewitt.
Grant Clinton 我们是Ted Dewitt-Clinton父母
Grant Clinton. Ted Dewitt-Clinton's parents.
打断下 他是不是那天和Quinn出去玩的哪个男孩?
Sorry, is he one of the boys who went out with Quinn the other night?
这个你们认得吧?
Does this look familiar?
口香糖?
Gum?
没错 你们女儿Daria的
Yes, from your daughter Daria.
二位要进来喝点什么吗?
Would you like to come in for a drink?
是酒吧 我猜
Alcohol, I presume.
现在我算知道那丫头怎么那样了
Well, now I see where she gets it.
我来烧一壶咖啡
I'll make a pot of coffee.
咖啡?!
Caffeine?!
我搞不太懂现在问题在哪
I don't really understand the problem here.
也难怪
Naturally.
你们这些人...
You people are happy
咀嚼着所谓现代社会的空虚物质就很开心了
chewing on the empty offerings of so-called modern society.
别让它们靠近我儿子的嘴 我们就感激涕零了
We'd just appreciate it if you kept them away from our son's mouth.
给我听好 嬉皮
Now, look here, hippy.
Daria有时确实比较棘手
Daria may be a handful sometimes,
但就因为她给你儿子口香糖 也没必要平白无故...
but just because she gave your kid some gum is no reason...
不单是口香糖
It wasn't just the gum.
她还给了他这个
She also gave him this.
披头士?
The Beatles?
我们保护他大半辈子 却没人在乎
We've tried so hard, and nobody seems to care.
这什么Ted是什么人?
Who the hell is this Ted kid?
还有我们的邻居们也都怪怪的
And what's happening to our neighborhood?
最开始是种起玉米 现在又这样?
First people growing corn, now this?
好吧 他可能是有点怪 但也有点可爱啊
Well, maybe he is a little weird, but he's also a little sweet.
这不重要吗?
Isn't that important?
重要不过他从没吃过口香糖这事实
Not as important as the fact that he never had gum before.
好萌 你和一个怪咖纠结起来了
This is so cute! You're involved with a kook!
我们没在纠结
We're not involved.
嗨 Daria 我找你来着
Hi, Daria! I was looking for you.
我雕了这条项链给你 谢谢你给我口香糖
I carved you this necklace, as thanks for the gum.
好美啊
That's beautiful.
我猜某人开始纠结了吧
I guess somebody here is involved.
纠结什么?
Involved in what?
嘿 有人想吃鹰嘴豆泥吗?
Hey, who wants some hummus?
我不能要这个 拿回去吧
I can't take this. Keep it.
但我希望你能收下
But I want you to have it.
我亲手做...
I made it...
Ted 我不能收下
Ted, I can't take it.
我们只是一起策划年鉴
We work together on yearbook.
不是要给对方做什么项链
We don't make jewelry for each other.
你不是在玩黑色幽默或者夸张吧 有吗?
You aren't being sarcastic or hyperbolic, are you?
没
No.
那... 我们年鉴策划会上见吧
Oh, then I guess I'll see you at yearbook.
做对事了?
Did the right thing?
是啊 有人给我亲手做了一条项链
Yeah. A guy makes me a necklace by hand
我却像收到核废料一样
and I act like it's nuclear waste.
当然 我做了对的事
Sure. I did the right thing.
好吧 现在你是在黑色幽默
Okay, now you're being sarcastic.
为什么我们之前从没听说过这个男孩?
But why haven't we heard about this boy before?
因为他是怪咖
Because he's a freak!
怪胎... 挺好 对吗?
Freak is, uh, good, right?
对 要是你们觉得加入邪教挺好的话
Yeah, if you think belonging to a cult is good.
另外 那个邪教里的每个人都穿得巨丑 还隔绝社会
Plus, everybody in the cult has to wear ugly clothes and be completely unsocial.
坏到不行
It's the worst!
邪教?
A cult?
Ted是什么人 你怎么从没跟我们说过
Who is Ted and why haven't you told us about him,
他有教唆你加入邪教吗?
and is he trying to get you to join a cult?
老兄...
Oh, brother.
他管自己叫老兄?
He calls himself brother?
叫Ted老兄啥的?
You mean like Brother Ted?
不是 我是说 "老兄 你们疯了吧"
No, like, "Oh, brother, you're all crazy."
Ted是一起做年鉴的好学生
Ted is a nice guy from yearbook.
他有点怪 但不在什么邪教
He's odd, but he's not in a cult.
最后说一次 我们没有在约会
And for the last time, we are not going out.
- 她显然在撒谎 - 绝对的 - 毋庸置疑
- She's obviously lying. - Absolutely. - No question.
能不能跟她谈谈 Quinn
Can't you talk to her, Quinn?
你干嘛不带着她去和你的那些朋友玩玩?
Why don't you set her up with one of your friends?
他们都还蛮正常的
They're all normal.
是啊 所以我要是真带Daria出去 他们会笑掉大牙的
Yeah, and that's exactly why they would laugh me out of town if I tried.
要是你肯 妈妈和我会给你甜头吃的
If you do, Mom and I will make it sweet for you.
什么甜头?
How sweet?
资助你给个人主页加声效怎么样?
How does your own web page sound?
不如给我来一双"咯噔咯噔咯噔"响...
Not as nice as the crunch-crunch-crunch sound
能在高中停车场穿出去的新鞋好呢
of a new pair of shoes on the high school parking lot.
成 Quinn 你最最好了
Deal! Quinn, you're the best.
搞不太懂为什么要帮一个平白无故的衰人找男朋友
I don't understand why we should help some random loser find a date.
看 这正是你们这种消极主义的人的想法
Now, that's exactly the kind of negative attitude that says,
"我只是时尚新闻的旁观者 不是时尚新闻的缔造者"
"I'm a fashion news reader and not a fashion news maker."
谢谢你 Sandi
Thank you, Sandi.
可我们找谁做她男朋友啊?
But who will we get to be her date?
Robert?
你希望我们能一直许你坐我们旁边这桌 对吧?
You like being allowed to sit at the other end of our table, right?
是啊 女士
Uh, yes, ma'am!
那我可有个任务要派给你
Then I have an assignment for you.
好啊 女士
Yes, ma'am!
我对Ted是不是太刻薄了?
Do you think I was too mean to Ted?
老兄
Oh, brother.
他不是什么老兄 也不在邪教里
He's not a brother, and he's not in a cult.
他只是很坦诚 很道义 很聪颖
He's just very honest and ethical and smart,
我不应该那么刻薄的
and I shouldn't have been so mean.
你还真心蛮在乎他的 有没有?
Whoa. You're really into him, aren't you?
没 但我真心喜欢因为他 我父母诚惶诚恐
No, but I do like the way he scares my parents.
你确定惹毛爸妈是建立良好关系的基础?
Are you sure annoying your parents is good grounds for a relationship?
罗密欧和朱丽叶不就是
It was for Romeo and Juliet.
Ted 我想我欠你一句对不起
Um, Ted, I think I owe you an apology.
你的项链很漂亮 我没有收下太无礼了
Your necklace was beautiful and I was a jerk for not taking it.
没关系
That's okay.
真的? 很好
Really? Good.
那我希望你能允许我请你吃披萨
Then I was hoping you'd let me buy you a slice of pizza.
坦白讲 Daria 我想也许你是对的
To be honest, Daria, I think maybe you were right.
我们应该把友情严格限定在年鉴策划的层面
We should keep our friendship on a strictly yearbook level.
等一下 你这是在埋怨我吗?
Wait a minute. Are you blowing me off?
这个 我爸妈警告过我传统学校的孩子可能会有点...
Well, my parents warned me that kids in conventional school can be kind of...
肤浅
shallow.
你觉得我肤浅?
You think I'm shallow?
你有点让我想到那个常能见到的人缘很好的女孩
You sort of remind me of that really popular girl I've seen around...
好像叫Quinn
Quinn, I think.
你认识她吗?
Do you know her?
你俩也许会比较处得来
You'd probably get along.
接下来《呕心小世界: 骗局还是幻影?》
Next on Sick, Sad World: hoax, or vision?
佛罗里达州有人声称见到了耶稣阵容... 在硬币上
Some people in Florida claim they've seen the face of Jesus... on a penny!
听着 如果从马上面下来
Look, when you get thrown off a horse,
你得重新站起来射杀它 对嘛?
you have to get back up and shoot it, right?
是的吧
I guess so.
话说我认识一个萌男 对你非常迷恋哦
So, I know this cute guy who's got a huge crush on you.
我们四人约会吧
Let's double!
得了 要么你是在整侮辱我的桥段
All right, this is either a plot to humiliate me,
要么就是需要我跟你出去 好帮你做点什么事
or you need me to go so I can do something for you.
好啦好啦 是把戏啦
Okay, okay, it's a trick.
如果你能来 爸妈会把我的宵禁时限延后半小时
If you come, Mom and Dad will extend my curfew by half an hour,
另外我在跟一个叨逼叨没完的叫Shawn的家伙约会
plus I'm dating this guy Shawn who never shuts up.
需要一个能说会道的人在身边
I want someone else there who can talk.
- 省省吧 - 十刀怎样?
- Forget it. - Ten bucks?
- 每小时 - 定了
- Per hour. - You're on.
算了 我变主意了
Nope, I've changed my mind.
拜托 Daria
Come on, Daria!
你想让老爸老妈亲自给你张罗男朋友吗?
You want Mom and Dad to set you up with somebody?
天呐
Oh, God.
赶紧收视准备吧
Now, hurry up and get ready.
我可不想吃鞋店的闭门羹
I want to get to the shoe store before it closes.
那... 我们今天约会都要玩些什么?
So, what exactly are we going to do on our date?
- 什么? - 别说话 Shawn
- What? - Quiet, Shawn.
我们就四处开车逛逛 转转便利店啥的 随便啦
We'll drive around; go to a convenience store... whatever.
随便做点年轻人爱干的事呗
The usual random teenage shenanigans.
是不是挺好? 跟她说话呀
Isn't that great? Talk to her!
那个 你怎么看...
So, what do you think
联合国下发的排放控制令对第三国家的影响?
of UN-mandated emission control laws for Third World countries?
理念崇高 但给出的时间表不切实际
Noble idea, but the UN's time table is unrealistic.
你怎么看?
How about you?
一样
Uh, same.
同意还是不同意:
Agree or disagree:
利用贸易禁令对抗侵犯人权的国家非常有效
trade embargoes are an effective way to deal
with countries that vi-o-late human rights.
同意 但面对中国这样的贸易伙伴巨头
Agreed, but with major trading partners like China,
我们的政府想找漏洞总能找到 你呢?
our government always finds a loophole. You?
是啊 一样
Yeah, same.
运动队和俱乐部能夺回他们在年鉴中的版面吗?
Can sports and clubs get their pages back in the yearbook?
好了 停车吧
Okay, stop the car.
- 什么? - 别说话 Shawn
- What? - Quiet, Shawn.
干嘛呀? 你俩处得多好呀
Why? You two are getting along great!
就凭Robert一个劲叫我Darcy
I should've known this wasn't a real date
该知道这不是什么约会
when Robert here kept calling me "Darcy."
抱歉 女士
Sorry, ma'am.
还叫"女士"
And "ma'am."
你想靠一场所谓的约会买我口软吗?
You were trying to buy my influence with a date?
美国人不都是这么干的 小伙伴
That's how we do it in America, comrade.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
- 什么? - 别说话 Shawn
- What? - Quiet, Shawn.
卡片顺序乱了
The cards got mixed up.
从现在开始 你吃午餐要另寻好桌了
From now on, you'll have to find a different table at lunch.
就下周一周
For the next week.
谢谢你 谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you.
什么?
What?
这张太棒了 痛感非常真实
This one's great. You can really feel the pain.
不过蹦床旁边不是应该有监护人的吗?
But aren't there supposed to be spotters at the trampoline?
我觉得 就算有监护人 她也免不了这一摔了
Well, I don't think even spotters could've stopped that fall.
总之 她没事
Anyway, she's fine.
其实她今天玩高低杠还摔了 所以显然是她自己的问题
In fact, she fell off the uneven bars today, so it was clearly her own fault.
暴民们来了
The angry villagers.
我们要拿回属于自己的年鉴版面
We want our rightful yearbook pages.
几个局外人对年鉴的制作方向指手画脚 这不公平
It's not fair that a couple of outsiders are dictating the way yearbook is done.
嘿 这两位局外人的建议非常中肯
Hey, these two outsiders made a good suggestion,
既然非常中肯 谁还管它公不公平
and if it's a good suggestion, who cares if it's fair?
坚守阵地 他们休想轰走我们
Stand your ground. They can't make us go.
嘿 大家伙
Hey, everybody!
干嘛不等卡仕曼特价促销季过去 我们再来这里摊牌?
Why don't we postpone the showdown until after the sale at Cashman's?
没那么快
Not so fast.
不给个说法 我是不会走的
I'm not leaving until I get results.
不如我们比握力一决胜负吧
Shall we settle it with a grip contest?
啥意思?
What's that?
这书呆子整我
The geek's hurting me!
宝贝儿 你还好吗?
Babe! Are you all right?
够了 我得去找工会谈谈
That's it. I'm talking to the union.
明年指导象棋俱乐部
Next year, chess club.
刚那套真厉害
That was a good trick.
静力训练
Isometric exercises.
我从十岁起就开始练了
I've been doing them since age ten.
Ted 我在想啊
Ted, I've been thinking.
我们能不能打破一下仅限年鉴的规则 去吃点披萨?
Can we bend our yearbook-only policy and maybe go out for some pizza?
听起来蛮不错的
Pizza sounds great!
真的?
Really?
披萨... 啥意思啊?
Pizza... what's it mean?
虽然不想说 但我得承认挺爱吃这种加工奶酪
I hate to say it, but I think I enjoy this processed cheese.
他们是怎么加工的啊?
What kind of process do they use?
你可以当它是无糖版的叮当和火火 (甜食)
It's a sugarless version of the one for Ding-Dongs and Ho-Hos.
叮当和火火
Ding-Dongs and Ho-Hos!
你太扯了
You're crazy!
所以我才会比较喜欢你吧
I think that's kind of why I like you.
我也喜欢你
I like you, too.
这才是最扯的地方
That's what's really crazy.
Barch老师
Ms. Barch.
我理解你要削减俱乐部在年鉴里的照片版面
I understand you're cutting the club pictures out of the yearbook.
我们打算将重点转移到...
We decided to shift the emphasis...
省省吧
Oh, save it.
你知道科学俱乐部的指导老师是谁嘛?
You know who the faculty advisor to the Science Club is?
就是那个一直赞助...
The same person who sponsors
朗岱尔高中"夺回夜幕"女子自卫俱乐部的人
the Take Back the Night Lawndale High School women's self-defense club.
话说 我们这种堕落的局外人吃完披萨都干嘛?
So, what do degenerate outsiders like us do after pizza?
我觉得可以去游乐场玩点电玩什么的
I thought maybe we could play some video games at the arcade.
别了吧 我看别了
Oh, no, I don't think so.
口香糖可以 但...
Gum is one thing, but...
电玩无害的
They're harmless.
再说了 就算你想排斥 也要先了解一下才好
Besides, if you're drafted, you need to know about them.
我倒是有点好奇
I guess I am a little curious.
好玩先生游戏厅
走着 伙计们 我们过去
Come on, dudes, let's get over there.
干嘛?
Why?
搅黄那个Darcy小妞和她的男朋友
So we can hassle that chick Darcy and her date.
干嘛?
Why?
想不起来了 不过应该很重要的
I can't remember, but I think it's important.
二位想玩什么?
What do you want?
城堡场景 水下宫殿 还是未来地狱?
Castle scenario, underwater paradise, futuristic dystopia?
选城堡吧
I guess the castle one.
没问题 老大
Okey-doke, boss.
Daria?
太过了 是吧?
It's too much, right?
我都有点受不了自己了
I feel a little sick myself.
这里并没如实反映中世纪社会的场景
It's not really representative of medieval society,
不过我得承认这是我这辈子见过最酷的场景了
but I have to say this is the coolest thing I've ever seen in my life!
这俩人是我们朋友
Uh, those are some friends of ours.
我们能加入吗?
Can we join in?
国王宝座
The royal throne!
太好了 我得坐下歇会儿
Good. I need to sit down.
先别急 怪胎们
Not so fast, weirdoes.
Robert?
请加我Robert大人 Darcy
That's Sir Robert, Darcy.
是Daria
Daria.
Ted?
我自学了十一世纪的舞剑手稿
I taught myself from the eleventh-century manuscript on swordplay.
太小菜了
It's easy.
没门 我不会善罢甘休的 跟上来
No way. I'm not going out like this. Come on!
走吧 Daria 我们能追上他们
Let's go, Daria. We can catch them!
我真的有点恶心了 你先去吧
This is making me nauseous. You go ahead.
Ted 游戏厅马上就要关门了
Ted, they're gonna close up pretty soon.
让他们先拔电源再说
They'll have to pull the plug, then.
我们还有很多战役 对不 伙计们?
We still have a lot of fight left. Right, men?
全都怪我自己
It's my own fault.
他最开始都不想去游戏厅的
He didn't even want to go to the arcade.
告诉过你
I told you:
第一次约会 顶多街头涂鸦或者瞎逛
first date, stick to vandalism and loitering,
可怎拦得住你非要与众不同
but you always have to be different.
抬头
Heads up.
你要做的 就是不要在手腕部位较劲
What you want to do is take the strain off your wrist
用上更多肘部的力量
and use more of your elbow.
像这样
Like this!
这样啊 你得在游戏机上亲自示范下
Oh, yeah! You gotta show me on the machine.
放学后怎么样?
Maybe after school?
好呀 你知不知道哪儿能搞点口香糖来的?
Okay. You don't know where we might obtain some gum, do you?
男生耍剑
Boys playing swords.
看来这事儿没看起来那么简单
I think that probably has some significance.
好吧
Oh, well.
至少我们还在为年鉴的事做有意义的斗争
At least we're still fighting the good fight at yearbook.
回头见了
I'll see you later.
Daria
Ah, Daria.
关于从运动队和俱乐部要过来的版面 我有点坏消息要说
I have some bad news about those pages we took from sports and clubs.
女人啊
Ow, woman!
我有点事要跟你们说
I have to tell you something.
你入了邪教了?
You joined the cult?
没有邪教
There's no cult.
我从年鉴组里退出了
I had to resign from yearbook.
是出于道义之选
It was a question of ethics.
又来?
Again?
别担心 她怎么也待了一礼拜呢
Don't worry, she was on staff for a week.
可以写进大学申请书里了
She can still put it on her college application!
不想问问道义上的问题吗?
No questions about ethics here.
那我还能拿到网页软件啥的吗?
So, then, can I keep the web page stuff?
我们已经给Quinn了
Actually, we gave it to Quinn.
Quinn? 她已经拆包装了吗?
Quinn? Did she remove the shrink-wrap?
我不信
I don't believe it.
全都你自己做的?
You did this yourself?
当然不是了
Of course not.
我在学校认识一个更萌的技术帝 他帮我搞定的
I had one of the cuter technical types from school set it up for me.
说清楚点
I had to ask.
抱歉你和那个什么Ted没有结果哦
Oh, sorry it didn't work out with that Ted guy.
是不是很有趣 我发现他其实还蛮酷蛮有趣的呢
Isn't it funny that now it turns out that he's sort of cool and interesting?
是啊 滑稽
Yeah, hilarious.
嘿 快来看
Hey! Check it out!
过去三小时 都有250人踩过我的主页了
My web page had twenty-five hundred hits in just the last three hours!
是嘛 我能轻易战胜
Really? I can beat that.
你都没有网页的好吧
You don't even have a web page.
是没 但我会踩
No... but I can hit.
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组